何だ…　こいつは…
Transmuters can use their aura
to alter objects' qualities.
アリの王　メルエム。 お前さんは 何にも分かっちゃいねえよ。
Conjurer. Somewhat akin to Transmuters,
Conjurers are able to manifest their aura.
人間の底すらない悪意を。
Emitters can propel their
aura like projectiles. Manipulator. Manipulators can use their auras to
control objects and creatures.
貴様は…
Specialist.
そう　貴様は…
Specialists are those with rare abilities
that don't fit in the other five classes.
その爆弾は　低予算で小型の上 驚くほどの殺傷能力を誇り
If you are successful, you will be hired, and begin training as a
bodyguard and a collector.
技術さえ確立してしまえば
The man talking was, most likely,
not the actual employer.
短期間での 大量生産が可能なことと 爆煙の特異な姿から
That only illustrates the distance
between the boss and me...
「貧者の薔薇」 「ミニチュアローズ」と呼ばれ 独裁小国家に好まれた
I shall reduce that distance to zero, until the employer feels that he
can trust me with his secrets...
「薔薇」は　延べ２５０を超える 国や地域で
First I need to curry their favor,
and win their trust.
その１０倍もの花を咲かせ
Nen x Users x Unite?
５１２万人の命を吸っていた
Hmm? The door won't open.
新たな生産を禁じる 国際条約が制定されはしたが
Three with guns.
現在　保有している「薔薇」の廃棄と 使用禁止には
Six with swords.
８割以上の国が難色を示し
Two more with swords above.
すでに作られた 数十万発の「種」は 今も各地で　開花の時を 静かに待っているのが現状だ
You guys did a good job
of concealing your presences, but you're too weak.
人とアリで　どこが違うのか
I don't even need to use my Nen...
奥の手に　これを選んだ ネテロの内に　そんな思いが 全くなかったと言い切れるか
Now I understand. So that's what's going on.
はるか先の黒煙と
I'll give you three seconds.
それが生んだであろう 空気の震えが意味するもの
One... Two... Okay. I get it.
同刻
Wh-What's going on?
プフの分身は ナックルと目が合った
They really were made from Nen. I could tell when I landed a punch, that I was hitting aura shaped like a human...
ユピーとの経緯から
However, I didn't realize it was his Nen. How did you know?
プフとも同様に 理解し合えるかもしれない
You were always careful to stand
next to others for camouflage.
そんなナックルの淡い期待は
But when I observed from above,
everything was clear.
粉々に打ち砕かれた
You were the only person not under attack.
((王が　タクトを振れば 奴らは悪魔にでもなるさ))
I assume they received the following order: Attack the nearest enemy.
プフの本体が気付いた
The assailants were given
simple instructions, so their attacks were also simple. However, it would take a skilled Nen user
その結果　見せた 分身の顔こそ　アリの本性
to control eleven human-sized
auras simultaneously.
会長は　王を倒したのか？ いや　結果が　どちらであれ…
A Nen user who would most
likely be a Manipulator. Given the size of auras involved, the Manipulator had to be
within a few meters.
ナックルは　決して 超えることのできない壁を
Which meant that the Nen user
プフの顔に見た
was inside this room.
うわっ！　壊れてる…
My name is Shachmono Tocino.
みんな　無事かな？
I'm actually a Hunter. I work for the boss here, so I will have seniority over you.
こりゃ　ひでぇ
Judging by those chains,
you must be a Manipulator...
たった３０分で すでに廃虚じゃねえか
Well, I hope you won't hold a grudge.
うわ！
Well, the four of you together
危ねぇ…。 イカルゴ！
Four? Is there another plant in the room?
キルア！
I'll assume that was meant as a diversion.
あぁ…。
I shall determine if there
are any other plants, before we all start becoming paranoid.
意志？
There.
あいつは　１人でピトーとやるって 決めたんだ。
You are a plant.
その代わり　決めた通りの シチュエーションなら
Th-That's ridiculous! What makes you say that?
最高のパフォーマンスを発揮する。
Your chain just started swinging.
要するに　俺達にできることは
That is dowsing.
あいつの邪魔をしないこと。
Huh? What's that?
で…　でも　もしも…。
Dowsing was originally
ああ　分かってるよ。
a technique for locating water
or metals underground.
それでも　あいつが 絶対的窮地に立ったら
But it was also used in divination.
迷わず助太刀に入ること。
I've heard of the technique being
employed as a lie detector.
そうか…　残るってのは そういうことなんだな
That still doesn't provide concrete proof that I'm a plant.
仮に　ゴンが現時点で 持てる能力の全てを出しても 到底　ピトーに勝つことは かなわない
He's probably right. Your heart began to pound as
soon as he pointed at you.
それどころか 俺達が加わったとしても ピトーには及ばないことを 全て承知で…
If you were innocent, your heart rate would have slowly increased, due to the stress of being wrongly accused.
残るっていうことは 共に死ぬということ！
But your heartbeat immediately sped up, before gradually slowing down.
ナックル達も 捜してるんだけど…。
The typical melody of a liar...
来るか？ もちろん！
Coming from both of you.
よし　行こう！
I'm convinced. Both of them accuse you.
王と護衛軍を分断し 会長に王討伐を託す。
It's possible that three out of five are
applicants and two are fakes. I can confirm
ノヴさんの言う通り
that he is not a plant.
その役目は十分に果たしたと思う。
Excuse me? I think you meant "she," not "he."
あとは　それぞれの考え方次第だ。
And it appears that you
are not a plant, either.
終えるか　続けるか。
My point is that we can't trust you! You two could be working together.
ここで すでに何度か落とした命だしな。 俺が納得できるまで　やる。
We won't get anywhere by standing around. No other choice, then.
I will have to settle this
matter on my own.
終わったな。
There's your explanation.
一体　どうして？ まだ 時間が来たわけでもないのに
"Any person who
responds untruthfully to
my question will burn."
施術が完了したことを 知ったのか
In other words, liars will burn in hell.
手術箇所は見えないように 隠したのに！
Here is my question.
終了した瞬間のわずかな弛緩が どこかに表れ
Are you a plant? No.
それに気付かれたなら…
What about you? I am not.
殺さねばならない
And you?
何としても
No.
こいつを 王のために！
Are you a plant? Yeah, that's right.
立て。
Think carefully before you answer.
俺達なら走ったほうが早い。
My answer is yes.
うっ　うん…。
Impressive.
うん…。
I'll reward you with some information.
ワダす　一体…？ できれば…　彼女を…　うっ！ 次　ゴタゴタ言ったら
My name is Squala. I don't have an official license, but I'm a Hunter with Manipulator skills.
そいつを殺す。
I've used my Manipulator abilities
す…　すいません！ ワダす　邪魔ですか？
to instruct something to
follow a certain order. You managed to unmask me, but that doesn't mean you'll
be able to escape alive...
あの…　ちょっと よく状況　分かんねくて…。
What was the something,
and what was the order? This wouldn't be much of
a test if I just told you.
分かった　行こう。
Even if you torture me, I won't talk. Huh?
ゴンの驚異的な勘の冴えを見て ピトーの本能は告げていた
This is my power, Instant Lover.
動いてはいけない チャンスは来る ペイジンへ向かう途中 いくらでも！
I am also a Manipulator. Anyone I kiss becomes my slave.
そのためには 何とかコムギを王の元へ！
M-M-Mistress...
ゴン　そいつ 「ハコワレ」で打っとくか？
Now, answer my question! What did you use your Nen on,
and what was your command?
万が一　奴が逃亡しても 場所が分かるし
Talk, quickly.
反撃して来たら 俺のポットクリンが盾になれるぜ。
If you don't answer, I'll stop treading on you! I'll talk! I'll talk! I am just a l-lowly dog trainer...
えっ？　えっ？　えっ？
A fearsome power.
ありがとう　ナックル。
I used my Nen on the dogs that run around this mansion.
でも　大丈夫。 俺は　ピトーを信じるよ。
For example, the Maltese were told to nip at a target's feet, to slow them.
だから　ナックルは 俺とピトーがカイトに会うまで
That's when the St. Bernard is to use
its large body to smother the target.
あのコを頼む。 えっ!?
At the same time, the Dobermans will rush in
ワ…　ワダすのことかしら？
and finish off the target... If the target still escapes,
the bulldogs will—
こいつ　コムギを…！ 人質に使う気か！
So the dog tamer has been
reduced to a pet, huh?
ピトーがカイトを 元に戻してくれたら
I only did it to make him talk.
すぐに彼女を解放するよ。
If I wanted a man as a pet,
I'd be more picky.
お前も俺を信じてくれるだろ？
That reminds me, I never did catch your name. I'm Basho.
ピトー。
As you've already seen, I'm a Conjurer.
ハァ　ハァ…。
I am Baise. Melody.
いいのか？　キルア。 ん？ ゴンと一緒に行かなくて。
I'd like to know your name. Would you tell us?
俺達…　いや キルアは心中する覚悟でいた
I refuse. We do not know if we'll
be working together.
なのに　ゴンは つれねえじゃねえかよ！
Yeah, that's true. We cleared the first test,
escaping the mansion, but the real test has just begun.
((ここからは 俺とピトーだけでいい))
We must locate one of the designated items, or we can't get the job.
いいんだよ もともと　そのつもりだったし。 何より あいつの考えを聞いて安心した。
If we're all interested in this job, we're bound to run into one other again.
危険なのは　一緒に行くことで 俺が逆にピトーに捕まること。
What is your opinion of this group? This particular group looks promising.
つまり　ピトーが 人質交換を思い付くほうが怖い。
More promising than him, at least.
こいつら… どんな修羅場をくぐれば
I will not require him for a while.
そんな発想ができるんだ？
Put him away for now.
大丈夫。
I trust you can handle that, Squala.
ゴンは　この目で見たから
Y-Yes...
何が何やら ワダすの頭では　さっぱり…
If I find one of the objects
and earn the contract, I will have passage to the
Yorknew City auction.
総帥様は　一体どこ？
Yes, I absolutely must attend! The Phantom Troupe will be there...
この人達は　何？
The band of thieves that slaughtered my fellow Kurta.
高熱によって　岩が赤黒く溶け
I will never forgive that act.
さながら 活火山の火口のごとき爆心地は
I shall track them down and utterly annihilate them!
俺は　間違っていた。
Hmm, so this is Greed Island.
奴らを殺すぞ。 王と共に
Looks like the memory card that
Kil found is the real deal.
一匹残らず！
You can probably decipher the data
and recreate the game, right?
あぁ…　くっ　うぅ…。
Yeah, we're almost to Yorknew.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
We'll see Kurapika and Leorio there.
王!!
I can't wait!
あっ！
We still have two weeks before
we're supposed to meet.
あぁ…。
Six months ago, I'd never have dreamed that we would come to Yorknew
for a reason like this.
うおぉ!! あっ！
We'll have to gather as much information
on Greed Island as possible beforehand. Yep, there might be information about Ging.
ユピーの咆哮は 不吉な全てを含んでおり その姿を確認する前から　すでに
Anyway, once I get the URL for the Hunter website from my brother,
we can check it out.